<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">ALEXIS CARREL</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">THE UNKNOWN MAN</string>
    <string name="article_text">The contributions and great advances accomplished by the dedicated work\n
        and extraordinary genius of <b>Alexis Carrel</b> (1873–1944) made possible the establishment of a new discipline,\n
        now considered to be transplantation. His pioneering Nobel Prize winning vessel suturing work (1912) plowed\n
        the way for an enhanced participation of surgical leaders in the demonstration of the feasibility of his newly\n
        introduced techniques. Even though most of the scientific disciplines associated with transplantation were in their\n
        infancy, the possibility of offering a means to realize the surgical face of transplantation presented an optimistic\n
        and new horizon for the developing field.\n
        \n
        Carrel remains an unknown man to the scientific and nonacademic readers of his life. In addition to his professional\n
        and well‐advanced scientific works, he was a mystical individual. He profoundly studied the human being, and through\n
        these studies he revealed himself. As one starts to unfold his complex personality through all his nonmedical writings,\n
        one begins to encounter the meticulous man, the impatient individual, the religious believer, the truth seeker and,\n
        paradoxically, the acceptor of clairvoyance and the supernatural. His popular and <i>the best‐selling</i> book of his times,\n
        <b>Man The Unknown</b> (1935), defined Carrels philosophical principles of life and confirmed his intense interest in\n
        discovering man and the most important part of him, the unknown element. For <i>Carrel</i>, man was as complex as he believed\n
        himself to be: the unknown man.\n
        \n
        Scientists did not take Carrels philosophical incursions kindly. They did not accept his views and criticized him in\n
        all his nonscientific developments. Carrel nevertheless characteristically disregarded his critics and charged himself\n
        to search for new concepts and forthcoming ideas. He maintained this resilience through all his existence and his work\n
        defines the Carrel as the complex man he was, as the spiritual student he attempted to be, and as the philosopher of the\n
        human race he so desired to be in his writings.\n
        https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1034/j.1399-0039.2002.00008.x </string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
</resources>